10 WITHWORTH AV, DRUMCONDRA, DUBLIN 3

MOBILE: 0838536331 EDUARDO@GMX.AT NATIONALITY: BRAZILIAN

VISA TYPE: STAMP4

ELIGIBILITY TO WORK: FULL TIME

CARLOS EDUARDO SANTIAGO

RESUME

I am a highly-qualified economist and I am currently studying for my Higher Diploma in Computing at Dublin Institute of Technology - DIT. At DIT, I am building a foundation of strong object oriented programming (OOP) and database management. My main OOP language is Python and I am open to code in other languages such as Java, C# and C++. I have 4 years of experience in an investment banking firm in Brazil, including 18 months of experience as Data Analyst using advanced Excel and VBA by writing so-called macros.

KEY SKILLS/

KNOWLEDGE

- Python
- SQL
- Html, CSS and JavaScript
- Advanced Excel and VBA (including work experience)

ACADEMIC EDUCATION

[DUBLIN INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY - DIT, DUBLIN - IRELAND]

Higher Diploma in Computing (2016-2017)

[UNIVERSIDADE FEDERAL FLUMINENSE - UFF, NITERÓI - BRAZIL]

Bachelor degree in Economics (2009-20013)

WORK EXPERIENCE

[DATA ANALYST AT GERAÇÃO FUTURO GESTÃO DE RECURSOS (ASSET MANAGEMENT) - RIO DE JANEIRO, BRAZIL]

[Sep 2014 - May 2016]

- Experience in creating reports to brokerage department with instructions for stocks trading such as instruments to trade, position, quantity, prices and strategy.
- Managing relationship with all key departments such as brokerage and custody, ensuring that data can be quickly delivered in accordance with the manager needs.
- Elaborate reports to the manager on request.
- Experience in advanced Excel and VBA by writing macros.

[BROKER AT GERAÇÃO FUTURO, RIO DE JANEIRO, BRAZIL]

[Mar 2013-Aug 2014]

Responsible for trading stocks for several strategies, such as: Long & Short,
Volatility, Skew, TWAP, VWAP, Volume participation, Cash & Carry and Basket

INVESTMENT ADVISOR AT GERAÇÃO FUTURO, RIO DE JANEIRO, BRAZIL]

[Mar 2012 - Mar 2013]

- Responsible for creating and maintaining a strong relationship with customers to recommend a balanced portfolio on Fixed Income funds, Equity, Multimarket and Real State Funds;
- Promote events and presentations to introduce customers to the company's new products.

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Portuguese (Native language); English (Fluent)